Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence /4212
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence
1943-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Labor- Management Documentation Center (LMDC)
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
/4212
7 cubic feet
7 linear ft.
Correspondence.
Correspondence generated in the process of building the Current Documents collection at the Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives.
3461763
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 05, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Scope and Contents
The correspondence is from various management and labor organizations in response to inquries for copies of collective bargaining agreements, personnel policies, and other documents.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4133: J. Gormly Miller Papers /4169: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files 6103: Labor Relations Board Files
Industrial relations -- United States; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives; Martin P. Catherwood Library. Labor-Management Documentation Center.
3461763
- Abbott Laboratories, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Ad Hoc Committee on the Triple Revolution, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  April 8 1964
- Administrative Management Society, 1964-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Addressograph Multigraph Corporation, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  November 6 1961
- Aerospace Corporation, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  June 17 1969
- Agway, Inc., 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Albany Felt Company, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  February 11 1965
- Alcan Aluminum Corporation, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ALCO Products Incorporated, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  March 6 1972
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  May 24 1963
- The Aluminum Association, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Aluminum Company of America, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Amerada Petroleum Corporation, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  August 2 1965
- American Airlines, 1959-1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- American Arbitration Association, 1967-1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- American Association of Industrial Editors, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- American Association of Industrial Management, National Metal Trades Association, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- The American Bankers Association, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- American Civil Liberties Union, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  October 27 1969
- American Documentation Institute, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- American Enka Corporation, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  January 28 1964
- American Foundation for Management Research, Inc., 1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  January 2 1968
- American Institute for Research, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- American Iron and Steel Institute, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- American Jewish Committee, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- American Library Association, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- American Machine and Foundry Company, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  March 2 1965
- American Management Association, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  February 7 1964
- American Medical Association, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  December 23 1964
- American Merchant Marine Institute, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- American Metal Climax, Inc., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- American Mining Congress, Henry I. Dworshak (Box 1, Folder 33)
- American Motors Corporation, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- American Oil Company, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- American Paper Institute, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  March 10 1975
- American Paper and Pulp Association, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- American Petroleum Institute, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  January 5 1965
- American Railway Car Institute, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  December 2 1964
- American Society for Personnel Administration, 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- American Society of Association Executives, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- The American Sugar Refining Company, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  May 16 1962
- American Symphony Orchestra League, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- American Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  March 25 1965
- American Trucking Associations, Inc., 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Anaconda Company Business Card (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Anchor Hocking Glass Corporation, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  June 1 1965
- Anthracite Board of Conciliation, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  February 18 1965
- Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  February 12 1969
- Arabian Oil Company (ARAMCO), 1964-1978 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Arizona Public Service Company, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  September 29 1965
- University of Arizona, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Armco Steel Corporation, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  June 5 1962
- Armour Food Company, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  October 13 1976
- Armour Leather Company, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  April 5 1967
- Armstrong Cork Company, 1962-1977 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Arrow Company (See Cluett, Peabody and Co.), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  July 29 1969
- Asia Foundation, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  March 1967
- Associated Builders and Contractors, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Associated Building Contractors of the Triple Cities, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 60)
  Business card
- Associated General Contractors of America Inc., 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Associated Industries of Cleveland, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Associated Industries of N.Y.S., Inc., 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Association of American Railroads, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Association of Washington Libraries, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  March 15 1971
- Association of Western Railways, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  October 1963
- Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway System, 1965-1974 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Atlantic Refining Company, 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Atlantic Richfield Company, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  March 11 1975
- Atlas Chemical Industries, Inc., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  December 11 1963
- Automatic Retailers of America, Inc., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Bache and Company, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Bank Street College of Education, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  February 1969
- Bankers Box Company, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  September 15 1964
- Bankers Trust Company, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Battelle Memorial Institute (Box 1, Folder 77)
  Business cards
- Bell Telephone Laboratories, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Benenson and Israelson, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  August 29 1969
- Bernan Associates, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Bethlehem Steel Company, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Bituminous Coal Operators' Association, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Blue Cross Association, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  March 27 1968
- Boeing Company, 1963-1978 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Borden Company, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  August 24 1959
- Boston University, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Branch Motor Express Company, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  November 9 1966
- Breed, Abbott and Morgan, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  May 1965
- British Information Services (Box 1, Folder 89)
- State University College at Buffalo, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Builders' Association of Chicago, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  October 23 1967
- Building Trades Employers Association of the City of New York, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Bulk Packaging and Containerization Institute, Inc., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  March 5 1965
- Bureau of Information of the Eastern Railways, 1957-1962 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., 1962-1969 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Burroughs Corporation, 1962-1978 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Business Archives Council, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  May 1967
- Business History Conference, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Business-Industry Political Action Committee, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- CIT Financial Corporation, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  November 5 1969
- California Institute of Technology (Box 1, Folder 101)
  Cards
- University of California, Institute of Governmental Affairs (Box 1, Folder 102)
- California State College at Fullerton, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- Canadian Civil Service Commission, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  October 24 1966
- Canada: Department of Labor Library, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- Canadian Department of National Health and Welfare, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  January 25 1966
- Canadian New Brunswick Department of Labor, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  March 30 1965
- Canadian Quebec (Province) Department of Labor, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  September 13 1965
- Canada Saskatchewan Ministry of Labor (Box 1, Folder 109)
  Business Card
- Canadair, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 110)
- Carborundum Company, 1964-1983 (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Jesse Carpenter, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  March 31 1970
- Carrier Corporation, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 113)
- Center for Community Change, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  March 1969
- Center for Information on America, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  October 1964
- Center for Productivity Motivation (Box 1, Folder 116)
- Center for the Study of Liberal Education for Adults (Box 1, Folder 117)
  Packing list
- Chamber of Commerce of the U.S., 1956-1968 (Box 1, Folder 118)
- Champion Paper and Fiber Company, 1956-1963 (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Chase Brass and Copper Company, 1962-1969 (Box 1, Folder 120)
- Chase Records Management, Inc., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  November 25 1964
- Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Co., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  December 6 1967
- Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of Maryland, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  March 9 1965
- Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of Virginia, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 124)
- Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad Company (Box 1, Folder 125)
- Chicago Mayor's Commission for Senior Citizens, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  July 26 1967
- Chicago Transit Authority, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 127)
- Chicago University AG Bush Library, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 128)
- Cities Service Oil Company, 1963-1975 (Box 1, Folder 129)
- Citizens' Crusade Against Power, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  January 7 1966
- City University of New York, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  November 15 1968
- Coast Federal Savings and Loan Association, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 132)
- Colgate-Palmolive Company, 1964-1978 (Box 1, Folder 133)
- Colonial Williamsburg (Box 1, Folder 134)
- Colorado, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 135)
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., 1965-1976 (Box 1, Folder 136)
- Columbia Gas System, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  September 12 1977
- Commerce and Industry Association of New York, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 138)
- Committee for National Health Insurance, 1968-1978 (Box 1, Folder 139)
- Commonwealth Edison Company, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  March and April 1964
- Community Council of Greater NY, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  Fall 1964
- Conference on Economic Progress, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 142)
- University of Connecticut, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  July 1963
- Connecticut General Life Insurance Company, 1966-1976 (Box 1, Folder 144)
- Connecticut Mutual Life Insurance Company (Box 1, Folder 145)
- Consolidated Edison, 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 146)
- Construction Industry Employers Association, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 147)
- Construction Employers Labor Relations Association of New York, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  February 1973
- Construction Industry Joint Conference, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 149)
- Consumers Power Company, 1965-1977 (Box 1, Folder 150)
- Container Transport International Inc., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  July 8 1964
- Continental Can, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  June 28 1976
- Continental Casualty Company, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  February 23 1965
- Continental Insurance Companies, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  August 20 1965
- Continental Oil Company, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  March 11 1965
- Control Data Corporation, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  February 22 1968
- Constance Cook, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 157)
- The Cooperative League of the USA, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  June 30 1966
- Copper Strike Information Bureau, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  December 21 1967
- Cornell University Associates, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 160)
- Cornell University NYSSILR Labor Liberal Arts Course, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 161)
- Corning Glassworks, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  May 6 1970
- Council for International Progress in Management (USA) Inc., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  October 13 1965
- Council for Latin America, Inc., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  November 1966
- Council for Profit Sharing Industries, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  July 24 1963
- Creative Education Foundation, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  December 10 1962
- Credit Union National Association (Box 1, Folder 167)
  Card
- Creole Petroleum Corporation, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  June 24 1965
- Cresap, McCormick and Paget, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  March 29 1965
- Crispell Brothers, Inc., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  September 18 1962
- Crouse-Hinds Company, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  January 6 1964
- Curtis Publishing Company, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 172)
- Dairymen's League Co-Operative Association, Inc., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  January 27, 1965
- Dan River Mills, 1962-1969 (Box 1, Folder 174)
- Dan Smoot Report, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  June 1963
- Dartnell Corporation, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 176)
  November 20 1962
- Daws, Lee A., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  June 1967
- Deere and Company, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 178)
- Denver Classroom Teachers, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  September and October 1967
- Detroit Edison Company, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 180)
- Detroit Public Library, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 181)
  October 8 1968
- Diamond Alkali Company, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  July 30 1964
- Development Dimensions, Inc., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  February 18 1975
- Dole Corporation, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 184)
- Douglas Aircraft Company, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 185)
- The Dow Chemical Company, 1962-1977 (Box 1, Folder 186)
- Drexel Institute of Technology, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 187)
- Dun and Bradstreet, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 188)
  Public Relations Division Business card
- Du Pont de Nemours and Company, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 189)
- Eastman Kodak Company, 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 190)
- Eaton Manufacturing Company, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 191)
  April 25 1962
- Ebasco Services Incorporated, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 192)
  April 18 1969
- Economist Intelligence Unit, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 193)
  June 27 1967
- Eddy-Rucker-Nickels Company, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 194)
- Electronic Industries Association, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 195)
  March and April 1967
- Elgin Sweeper Company, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 196)
  March 21 1962
- Elgin Watch Company, Inc., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 197)
  March 31 1975
- Eli Lilly and Company, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 198)
  January 20 1970
- Elliott Company, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 199)
- Employees Retirement Fund of the Electrical Manufacturing Industry, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 200)
  January 29 1965
- Employers Association of Detroit, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 201)
  July 1964
- Employers Association of Greater Chicago, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 202)
  October 26 1966
- Equitable Gas Company, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 203)
  June 10 1965
- The Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 204)
  May 13 1968
- Esso Research and Engineering, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 205)
  November 26 1962
- Ethyl Corporation, 1962-1968 (Box 1, Folder 206)
- Extrudo Film Corporation, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 207)
  August 31 1964
- Exxon Company, U.S.A., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 208)
  June 2 1976
- Facing Reality Publishing Committee, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 209)
  August 22 1962
- Fairchild Publications, Inc., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 210)
  September 7 1962
- Falstaff Brewing Corporation, 1958-1965 (Box 1, Folder 211)
- Farrel-Birmingham Company, Inc., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 212)
- Federal Employees News Digest, Inc., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 213)
  November 20 1973
- Federal Labor Relations Authority, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 214)
- Federal Professional Association, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 215)
  July 6 1966
- Federal Reserve Bank of Boston, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 216)
  April 20 1962
- Federal Reserve Bank of New York, 1964-1978 (Box 1, Folder 217)
- Federated Employers of the Bay Area, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 218)
- Financial Executives Institute, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 219)
- Firestone Tire and Rubber Company, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 220)
  June 5 1969
- First National City Bank New York, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 221)
- First National Bank of Maryland, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 222)
  October 8 1965
- First National Bank of Nevada, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 223)
  October 22 1964
- 1964 (Box 1, Folder 224)
- First Pennsylvania Banking and Trust Co., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 225)
  February 10 1965
- Fischer and Porter Co., 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 226)
- Florida Power Corporation, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 227)
  November 5 1964
- Food Fair Stores, Inc., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 228)
  June 19 1969
- Ford Foundation, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 229)
- Ford Motor Company, 1953-1965 (Box 1, Folder 230)
- Foster, Campbell, Lindemer and McGurrin, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 231)
  March and October 1966
- Foundation for Research on Human Behavior, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 232)
  October 27 1966
- Gay-Tifft, Eugene and Lola, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 233)
  February and May 1966
- General Dynamics, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 234)
- General Electric Company, 1955-1969 (Box 1, Folder 235)
- General Electric Foundation, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 236)
  May 26 1964
- General Foods Corporation, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 237)
- General Motors Corporation, 1957-1965 (Box 1, Folder 238)
- General Motors Institute, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 239)
  April and May 1969
- General Telephone Company of Indiana, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 240)
- General Telephone Company of Michigan, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 241)
- Gill, Lewis M., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 242)
  June and November 1963
- Gimbels, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 243)
- Glass Container Manufacturers Institute, Inc., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 244)
  December 30 1965
- B.F. Goodrich Company, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 245)
  October 23 1964
- Goulds Pumps, Inc., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 246)
  September and October 1965
- Grand Union Company, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 247)
  November 22 1965
- Great Britain, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 248)
- Greater Detroit Board of Commerce, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 249)
  July 27 1966
- Great Lakes Carbon Corporation, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 250)
  June 14 1962
- Greenleigh Associates, Inc., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 251)
  May 1969
- Group Health Association of America, Inc., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 252)
  January 1965
- Group Research, Inc., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 253)
  August 6 1963
- Grumman Aircraft Engineering Corporation, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 254)
  November 23 1965
- Harper and Row, Publishers, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 255)
  July 15, 1963
- Harris Trust and Savings Bank, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 256)
  June and July 1965
- Harvard University, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 257)
- Hawaiian Telephone Company, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 258)
  October 28 1977
- Health Information Foundation, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 259)
  May 1 1961
- Health Insurance Institute, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 260)
  December 14 1964
- H.J. Heinz Company, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 261)
  June 28 1967
- Held, Herbert, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 262)
  June 7 1967
- Hercules Powder Company, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 263)
- Hershey Chocolate Corporation, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 264)
  July 15 1964
- Hildebrand, George C., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 265)
  November 18 1969
- Hill, Olney W., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 266)
  Aril and July 1964
- Hill and Knowlton, Inc., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 267)
  March 17 1965
- Hosking, William, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 268)
  February and April 1963
- Hospital Association of N.Y.S., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 269)
  October 20 1967
- Hotels, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 270)
- Humble Oil and Refining Company, 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 271)
- Hydro-Electric Power Commission of Ontario, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 272)
  August 1964
- Illinois Labor History Society, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 273)
  August 1970
- Illinois Retail Merchants Association, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 274)
  June 7 1965
- University of Illinois, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 275)
- University of Indiana (Box 1, Folder 276)
- Indiana Lumber and Builders Supply Association, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 277)
  February and March 1962
- Indiana State Chamber of Commerce (Box 1, Folder 278)
- Industrial Education Films, Inc., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 279)
- Industrial Relations Institutes, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 280)
- Industrial Training Council of N.Y., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 281)
- Institute of Life Insurance, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 282)
- Insurance Economics Society of America, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 283)
  February 4 1965
- Interchemical Corporation, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 284)
  April 1967
- International Business Machines Corporation, 1962-1968 (Box 1, Folder 285)
- International Chamber of Commerce, Inc. U.S. Council, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 286)
- International Harvester Company, 1964-1978 (Box 1, Folder 287)
- International Labor Office, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 288)
  July 8 1969
- International Nickel Company of Canada, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 289)
- International Shoe Company, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 290)
  April and May 1965
- Investment Bankers Association of America, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 291)
  December 1964
- Investment Company Institute, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 292)
  December 17 1962
- Iowa University, 1962-1968 (Box 1, Folder 293)
- Ireland, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 294)
  August 22 1966
- Ithaca College, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 295)
  February 17 1969
- Japan, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 296)
  April 1 1968
- John Hancock, 1962-1983 (Box 1, Folder 297)
- Johns-Manville Corporation, 1962-1968 (Box 1, Folder 298)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Corporation, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 299)
  September 29 1967
- Johnson and Johnson, 1962-1969 (Box 1, Folder 300)
- Joint Industry Board of the Electrical Industry, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 301)
- Joseph V. Baker Associates, Inc., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 302)
  May 19 1969
- Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corporation, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 303)
  October 11 1963
- Kaiser Steel Corporation, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 304)
  September 2 1964
- Kaman Aircraft Corporation, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 305)
  May 1963
- Kansas Department of Human Resources, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 306)
  May 11 1977
- W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 307)
  October 21 1964
- Kelly, James Labor Relations Consultant, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 308)
  January and February 1968
- Kemper Insurance, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 309)
  August 6 1964
- Kennecott Copper Corporation, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 310)
- Kohler Company, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 311)
  May 3 1967
- Kroehler Manufacturing Company, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 312)
- Kroger Company, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 313)
- Lake Carriers' Association, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Leadership Resources, Inc., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  July 5 1966
- Leeds and Northrup Co., 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Lever Brothers Company, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  April 30 1964
- Libbey-Owens-Ford Glass Company, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  March 10 1970
- Libby, McNeill and Libby, 1964-1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Life Office Management Association, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  August 1966
- Liggett and Myers Incorporated, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  March 8 1976
- Lincoln Electric Company, 1962-1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Lincoln Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  October 17 1963
- Litton Industries, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Lockheed Aircraft Corp., 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)